wisdomjobsgulf.com 2016-04-02

# Privacy Policy | Wisdomjobsgulf.com

### Privacy Policy

#### Introduction

We,wisdomjobsgulf.com a part of Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd., are committed to respect your online privacy and recognize your need for suitable protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.

Personal Information" contains any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. For further information, you can visit Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd. web pages with confidentially or without revealing any personal information about yourself.

#### Technologies used for tracking

Some of our web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is denoted as a small text file used to collect information about web site activity. Some cookies and some other technologies may serve to remind personal information previously indicated by a web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

You may set most browsers to notify, if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. But please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the web site.

Tracking technologies may record information such as internet domain and host names; internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; click stream patterns; and dates and times of the accessing details of the user. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our web site. We may also analyze the information that does not contain personal information for trends and statistical analysis.

#### External Services

Third parties provide certain services available on www.wisdomitservices.com on Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd. Behalf of Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd..The provided information may contain personal information, that Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd. collects on the web to third-party service providers to help us deliver programs, products, information, and services. Service providers are also an important means by which Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd. maintains its web site and mailing lists. Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd. will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect personal information on Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.s behalf.

Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.does not intend to transfer personal information without your consent to third parties, who are not bound to act on Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.s behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.s policy to sell personal information collected online without your consent. 

#### Your Commitment

By using this Web site, your consent to the terms of our online privacy policy and to Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.s processing of personal information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where ‘Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd. collects personal information on the web. 

  * We ensure maximum security standards to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data of yours.

#### Security Measures

We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.

  * We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.

#### Updating your information

  * We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personally identifying information for many of our services. For more information, please see the help pages for each service.

#### Restricting Information Sharing and Disclosure

**Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.'** does not lease, sell, or share personal information about you with third party(save with your consent) or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services youve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd. under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.communicate with you about offers from Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd. and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We consider that it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We have the right to transfer information about you incase Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.is acquired or merged with another company. In this event, Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd. will intimate you before information is transferred to the new company and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd. Is also having the right to display the targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with you may view, or click on targeted ads to meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.

  * Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd. does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted advertisement. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the advertisement.
  * Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd. advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies.

Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.works with business partners like vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers of various industries and business. For more information regarding services provides and other products please go through our detailed reference links.

#### Confidentiality and Security

  * We provides limited access to personal information about you to employees, who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
  * We also have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that meet the terms with legal parameters in India to protect personal information about you. We seek to ensure compliance with the requirements of the Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules made there under to ensure the protection and preservation of your privacy policy.

#### Contact Information

Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltdwelcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement at the contact address given at the website. We invite your concerns about contravention of this Privacy Policy; Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.will employ all commercially reasonable efforts to address the same. 

**Note :** The terms in this agreement may be changed by Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.at any time. Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.is free to offer its services to any client/prospective client without restriction.
